// For the answer value, please use the letter of the correct answer
module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'When did a the deadliest natural disaster in the U.S. cause an estimated eight thousand deaths in Galveston?',
  a: '1956',
  b: '1926',
  c: '1900',
  d: '1999',
  answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was the infamous pirate who formed a settlement called Campeche on Galveston Island?',
  a: 'Jean Lafitte',
  b: 'Blackbeard',
  c: 'Calico Jack',
  d: 'Captain Obvious',
  answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the nickname of Galveston, Texas?',
  a: 'The Jewel of the Gulf',
  b: 'The Oleander City',
  c: 'The Other Port A',
  d: 'The Garden City',
  answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the Victorian-themed Christmas festival held every year in Galveston called?',
  a: 'Posh Holly Row',
  b: 'Scrooge on the Seawall',
  c: 'Pride & Prejudice & Elves',
  d: 'Dickens on the Strand',
  answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Galveston was the home of the inventor of ____?',
  a: 'air conditioning',
  b: 'condensed milk',
  c: 'the Slapchop',
  d: 'muzak',
  answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'The average temperature in Galveston during the summer months is?',
  a: '81 degrees',
  b: '99 degrees',
  c: '75 degrees',
  d: '105 degrees',
  answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the current length of the Galveston seawall?',
  a: '3.50 miles',
  b: '10.1 miles',
  c: '5.5 miles',
  d: '25.2 miles',
  answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Before it was known as Galveston, what did French explorer La Salle name the island?',
  a: 'San Louis',
  b: 'San Petit',
  c: 'San Macron',
  d: 'San Diego',
  answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'In Galveston, it is specifically illegal to have a _____ run loose on the beach.',
  a: 'tiger',
  b: 'platypus',
  c: 'gecko',
  d: 'camel',
  answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'This Heisman Trophy winner grew up in Galveston, Texas.',
  a: 'Andre Ware',
  b: 'Jim Plunkett',
  c: 'Marcus Allen',
  d: 'Bo Jackson',
  answer: 'a'
  }
]

